servicesdirectory.us 2016-10-29

# Privacy Policy | Find Internet, Cable TV, and Phone Service in your Area

This privacy statement discloses what type of information we gather and how we use it. Privacy is one of our core company values, and your privacy on the  internet is important to us.

What information do we collect and how do we use it?

We gather address, phone number, and other user data provided when performing an internet service availability search or when signing up for high speed internet services. When checking for internet service availability we ask you for contact information (such as your name, address, and phone number). We use the information we gather to determine if your address and/or telephone line is within range of high speed internet service offerings, and to contact you should there be any questions regarding your order or to notify you of the status of your order. We may also use the information at a later date to send you information about high speed internet services and special offers.

How do we protect customer information?

We have security measures in place to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We restrict access to personal information to employees & third parties who require the information in order to deliver high speed internet service to you.

Do we disclose information we collect to outside parties?

When required we may need to provide information such as your address and/or phone number to outside parties (i.e. telephone companies, cable companies, etc.) in order to check availability of high speed internet service to your location. We will not share or disclose information about you except (a) when required to do so by legal process, such as a court order, (b) in emergencies when someone's safety is at risk, or (c) when reasonably necessary to protect our rights or property.

Is shopping online really safe?

The truth is that you take less risk ordering online than you do when using your credit card at a restaurant or department store. When you swipe your credit card at the local store, your credit card number is encrypted and transmitted over a phone network. All of our partners use Secure Socket Layering Technology (SSL) to encrypt your personal information, including your name, address and credit card number, before it is transmitted over the Internet. SSL is state-of-the-art technology, incorporating sophisticated encryption capability, digital certificates, and online authentication. SSL is currently the industry standard for secure online transactions.

Privacy policy changes

In the future, we may use customer and visitor information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our practices change, we will post an updated policy statement to our website as a way to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of any new uses of information. We reserve the right to make changes to this policy at any time. If the change involves a reduction in privacy protection of any kind, a notice will be posted here explaining any change.
